He's not from around here...
The Wraith is a action, science fiction film directed by Mike Marvin.
Packard Walsh and his motorized gang control and terrorize an Arizona desert town
where they force drivers to drag-race so they can 'win' their vehicles.
After Walsh beats the decent teenager Jamie Hankins to death after finding him with his girlfriend, a
mysterious power creates Jake Kesey, an extremely cool motor-biker who has a car which is invincible.
Jake befriends Jamie's girlfriend Keri Johnson, takes Jamie's sweet brother Bill under his wing and
manages what Sheriff Loomis couldn't; eliminate Packard's criminal gang the hard way...
Jake Kesey / The Wraith, played by Charlie Sheen.
Packard Walsh, played by Nick Cassavetes.
Keri Johnson, played by Sherilyn Fenn.
Sheriff Loomis, played by Randy Quaid.
Billy Hankins, played by Matthew Barry.
Rughead, played by Clint Howard.
The Wraith is a 1986 independently made American action-fantasy film, produced by John Kemeny, written and
directed by Mike Marvin, and starring Charlie Sheen, Sherilyn Fenn, Nick Cassavetes, and Randy Quaid.
The film was theatrically released November 21, 1986, on just 88 screens in the United States by
New Century Vista Film Company (later New Century Entertainment Corporation).
The film explores themes of sheriff, car race, cemetery, killing, arizona.
The tone is thought_provoking.